(+91) 9119620847 Hyderabad, India prashant@cometlabs.in

Prashant Katiyar

Tech Entrepreneur | Product Manager | Developer Relations LinkedIn: prashant-milan-katiyar

Portfolio: prashantkatiyar.com GitHub: prashantkatiyar9777

Startup Founder with 3 years of experience building SaaS products in Developer Tools, Hiring, Web-3 and Retail Tech Startups, which generated over \$ 3.5 Million in revenue. I run a community of 1,20,000+ Developers, providing tools to show proof of work. I also raised \$ 150K (₹ 1.1 Cr) in Venture Capital for my startup in 2nd year of college.

EXPERIENCE

Co-Founder & Chief Product Officer

May 2021 - Present

CometLabs

Hyderabad, India

- Led development of a cloud-based IDE, similar to Replit, utilizing GenAI for intricate code analysis and project evaluations.
- Secured INR 1.1 Cr preseed funding, served a thriving community of 120K developers & 18,000 active users.
- Built product from UI design to MVP; later supervised an 11-member engineering team.
- Established partnerships with GitHub and Vercel for seamless integrations to enhance the developer experience.
- · Adopted Agile workflows & Sprint Planning using tools like Confluence, Jira, Notion, Miro, Trello, etc.
- Outperformed competitors: 40% speedier load, 25% better efficiency, and 20% less browser memory usage within 8 months.

Associate Product Manager

Dec 2020 - Sep 2021

Hapramp Studios Gurgaon, India

- Headed Creator Studio division: launching 3 major updates & initiating 4 beta tests within a 5-month timeframe.
- Drafted PRDs for Binance Wallet & KYC integration, achieving 50K+ DAU and boosting GTV.
- Conducted A/B Testing to improve performance, amplifying ASPU by 37%, Token Sales by 42% while trimming TTV by 20%.
- Coordinated closely with a 13-member Tech & Design team to ensure timely project delivery.
- Explored new revenue models by introducing NFT Minting after analyzing Web3 Market, increased revenue by 12%.

Product Manager Intern & FullStack Developer

May 2020 - Dec 2020

Moptra Infotech

Noida/Remote, India

- Collaborated with Devs to refine a supply chain tool, enhancing user satisfaction by 15%.
- Integrated Amplitude, Google Analytics & CRM with e-commerce platforms, grew engagement by 12%.
- Led design sprints, optimized JIRA product roadmaps, and crafted PRDs based on user feedback.
- Conducted A/B tests on the e-commerce platform, driving a 10% boost in user conversions.

SKILLS

Product Management Tools Jira, Trello, Notion, Miro, Amplitude, Mixpanel, Metabase, Google Analytics

Product Design Tools Balsamiq, Lucid Charts, Figma, Canva, Retool **Programming Languages** SQL, C, C++, Javascript, Python, Bash

Framework Technologies ReactJS, NextJS, Tailwind, AWS, NodeJs.

Core Competencies Product Strategy, Business Analysis, User Research, Community Building, Persona Creation, Wireframing, Mockups, PRD, Product Roadmap, Agile Methodology, Sprint Planning, TDD,

Risk Management. UAT, A/B Testing, Product Analytics, Success Metrics, KPIs

EDUCATION

B. Tech. (ECE), Indian Institute of Information Technology (IIIT), Guwahati
Entrepreneurial Studies (Seed Spark) , Stanford University Graduate School of Business

Apr 2023

July 2023

ACTIVITIES

Top 30 Finalist - HYSEA 10X Product Awards & Expo, Hyderabad
Top 5 Finalist - EO Global Student Entrepreneur Awards (GSEA), Goa & New Delhi
Founder - IIITians Network: Community of 59500+ Developers from IITs, IIITs

2023

2023

2021 - 2022

PROJECTS

PRDs / Teardowns

- CometLabs PRD: Cloud-based code analysis with static tools, ML insights, and integrated developer tools.
- CodeSandBox Product Teardown: Analyzed features, user feedback, and suggested improvements in CodeSandbox IDEs.

Product Case Studies

- Dunzo App: Conducted an in-depth analysis, highlighting its market strategy and potential.
- FamPay App: A leading youth-focused financial platform, detailing its features, market positioning, and growth opportunities.